Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are you ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids: Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：是的，是的，队长。
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:   Aye, aye,
Captain.
孩子们：是啊是啊
队长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
SpongeBob: Gotta hurry, Gary.
海绵宝宝：加里，得快点。
The sooner I get to bed,
the sooner I'll get to sleep
我越早睡觉，
我越早睡觉
and the sooner I get to sleep,
the sooner I'll wake up
我越早睡觉，
我会越早醒来
and the sooner I wake up,
oh ho ho...
而且我越早醒来，
哦嗬嗬...
The sooner I can go
to work at the best job
in the whole world...
我越早可以走
从事最好的工作
在全世界...
The Krusty Krab.
蟹堡王。
Now to just put on these
sleepy-time blinders
现在穿上这些
睡眠时的眼罩
before I run excitedly to bed.
在我兴奋地跑去睡觉之前。
Well, good night, Gar'.
好吧，晚安，加尔。
Meow.
喵。
I'm just gonna
turn out the lights...
我只是要
关掉灯...
clickety-poo...
咔哒声...
And close my eyes
and go to sleep.
然后闭上我的眼睛
然后去睡觉。
Just close my eyes
只要闭上我的眼睛
and go to sleep.
然后去睡觉。
Grrr, grrr.
咕噜咕噜。
Just close my...
只要关闭我的...
Maybe if I run around,
it'll tire me out.
或许如果我到处跑的话
它会让我疲惫不堪。
Oh, I just gotta
get some sleep!
哦，我只需要
睡一会儿吧！
There's only one thing for this.
这只有一件事。
Ahh, that's the stuff.
啊啊，就是这个东西。
A glass of warm snail milk.
一杯温热的蜗牛奶。
Ah.
啊。
Da... Why isn't it
working?
达...为什么不是
工作？
Oh, Gary, what happened?
哦，加里，发生了什么事？
Ah, I'm late for work.
啊，我上班迟到了。
Oh, my gosh,
only 20 seconds to go.
哦，天哪，
只剩下 20 秒了。
What the... bridge out?
什么……桥出来？
Hopscotch?
跳房子？
Ah...!
啊...！
No...!
不...！
I'm late.
我来晚了。
What's Mr. Krabs gonna say?
蟹老板会说什么？
Eh...
呃……
: Tardy pants.
: 迟到的裤子。
You, sir, are a tardy pants.
先生，你真是个迟到的人。
Wait 'til Mr. Krabs finds out.
等到蟹老板发现为止。
You better think of something
to save your job.
你最好想点办法
来保住你的工作。
Man on speaker: One Krabby Patty
and Krabby Fries
演讲者：One Krabby Patty
和蟹黄薯条
for table four.
对于表四。
Order up.
订购吧。
Here you go, sir.
给你，先生。
One Krabby Patty, Krabby
Fries and a Krabby Drink
一颗蟹肉饼，蟹肉饼
薯条和蟹黄饮料
in three seconds flat.
三秒内平。
Spill at table...
洒在餐桌上...
I'm on it.
我正在做。
Nothing a dedicated "on time"
employee can't handle.
没有什么是专门的“准时”
员工无法处理。
Kiddies get a free touch-up.
孩子们可以获得免费修饰。
Ha... All done.
哈……都完成了。
Hey, SpongeBob.
嘿，海绵宝宝。
No...!
不...！
Please don't throw me
out in the street.
请不要扔我
在街上。
I am so sorry
for what I did.
我很抱歉
为了我所做的事。
What'd you do?
你做了什么？
I was a minute
late for work.
我是一分钟
上班迟到了。
A minute late?
迟到一分钟？
A whole 60 seconds.
整整60秒。
Well, uh, don't do it again.
好吧，呃，不要再这样做了。
No, no, you have
to punish me.
不不不，你有
来惩罚我。
What?
什么？
OK, uh... Then wipe
down the salad bar.
好吧，呃...然后擦
沿着沙拉吧。
Aye, aye, sir.
是啊，是啊，先生。
Now good night.
现在晚安。
I love it here, Mr. Krabs.
我喜欢这里，蟹老板。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, sheesh.
是啊，是啊，是啊，谢希。
If you love it
here so much
如果你喜欢它
这里就这么多
why don't you
just live here?
你为什么不
就住在这里吗？
Eh... Uh.
呃……呃。
Something's not right.
有什么不对劲。
What is it?
它是什么？
Do I miss my old clock?
我想念我的旧钟吗？
Maybe it's my own bed?
也许这是我自己的床？
Oh, that's it.
哦，就是这样。
I'll make the Krusty
Krab just like home.
我会做库斯蒂
蟹蟹就像在家里一样。
What do you say, Gary?
你说什么，加里？
: Meow.
: 喵。
Mr. Krabs: SpongeBob.
蟹老板：海绵宝宝。
What in Neptune's navy
is goin' on here?
海王星海军有什么
正在这里进行吗？
SpongeBob reporting
for duty, sir.
海绵宝宝报道
为了职责，先生。
How long you
been here?
你多久了
来过这里吗？
All night, sir.
整个晚上，先生。
All night?
整晚？
That's right, I'm gonna
live here from now on
没错，我要
从现在开始住在这里
so I'll never ever
be tardy pants again.
所以我永远不会
又是迟到的裤子。
Hold on, this ain't
no hotel, boy.
等等，这不是
没有旅馆，孩子。
Here's my first
month's rent.
这是我的第一个
一个月的租金。
Rent?
租？
OK.
好的。
Well, let's get ready
for the customers.
好吧，让我们做好准备
为客户。
Start scrubbing the grill and...
开始擦洗烤架，然后...
Well, then, start
cookin' some--
那么，开始吧
煮一些——
Done.
完毕。
All that before we've even
opened our doors, sir.
所有这一切都发生在我们之前
打开我们的门，先生。
OK.
好的。
Then get cleaned up,
you look a mess.
然后清理干净，
你看上去一团糟。
Ew, guess I could use
some freshening up.
呃，我想我可以用
一些清爽。
Jammed again.
又卡住了。
SpongeBob:
Oh, hi, Squidward.
海绵宝宝：
哦，嗨，章鱼哥。
SpongeBob, what are
you doing here?
海绵宝宝，什么是
你在这里做什么？
Oh, I live here now.
哦，我现在住在这里。
In the dishwasher?
在洗碗机里？
No, at the Krusty Krab.
不，在蟹堡王。
Now, if you'll excuse me.
现在，请原谅。
SpongeBob living
at the Krusty Krab?
海绵宝宝生活
在蟹堡王？
Wait a minute,
if he's living here
等一下，
如果他住在这里
that means he won't be
living next to me.
这意味着他不会
住在我旁边。
Ah...
啊...
Must be a full moon.
一定是满月。
Mr. Squidward?
章鱼哥先生？
Just saying good night
to SpongeBob, Mr. Krabs.
只是说晚安
海绵宝宝，蟹老板。
Sweet dreams, SpongeBob.
祝你好梦，海绵宝宝。
You look so much comfier here
than in your old home.
你在这里看起来舒服多了
比在你的老家。
Won't you miss me living
next-door, Squidward?
你不会想念我活着吗
隔壁，章鱼哥？
Pfft...
No.
噗……
不。
Coming, Eugene.
来了，尤金。
Whoo-hoo-hoo.
呼呼呼。
Good night's sleep,
here I come.
晚安，睡个好觉
我来了。
...and when I went home
at night, guess what?
……当我回家时
晚上，你猜怎么着？
He wasn't there?
他不在场吗？
Right.
正确的。
And, and when I woke up
in the morning...
而且，当我醒来时
早上...
Can I just get my change?
我可以拿零钱吗？
...he still wasn't there!
……他还没来！
Come on, man, my change.
来吧，伙计，我的零钱。
Oh, here you go.
哦，给你。
Yeah, well, thank--
是的，好吧，谢谢——
Oh, real funny, buddy.
哦，真有趣，伙计。
Two socks and a pair
of tighty whities?
两只袜子和一双
紧身白人？
Socks and
what the?
袜子和
什么？
SpongeBob, why is your underwear
in the cash register?
海绵宝宝，你的内衣怎么了
在收银机里？
Well I had to put
'em somewhere
好吧，我不得不把
他们在某个地方
and my underwear drawer is all
filled up with Krabby Patties
我的内衣抽屉里全是
里面装满了蟹黄馅饼
and the freezer's all filled up
with my snowflake collection.
冰箱已经满了
和我的雪花收藏。
So I put the cash from the cash
register in the pickle jar.
所以我把现金从现金里拿出来
注册到泡菜罐子里。
What?
什么？
Oh, lighten up,
Squidward.
哦，轻一点，
章鱼哥。
'Tis harmless
tomfoolery.
这是无害的
愚蠢的行为。
Do you wanna know
where the mustard is?
你想知道吗
芥末在哪里？
Meow.
喵。
Eww.
呃。
Well, he may be twice
as annoying at work
好吧，他可能是两次
工作中很烦人
but it still beats having
him as a neighbor.
但它仍然胜过拥有
他作为邻居。
Ow.
噢。
Ah.
啊。
♪ Laundry song,
la-la-la ♪
♪ 洗衣歌，
啦啦啦♪
♪ Sing about your laundry
all day long ♪
♪ 唱出你要洗的衣服
一整天♪
♪ La-la-la-la
laundry song ♪
♪ 啦啦啦啦
洗衣歌♪
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
You can't be hanging
your delicates in me
customers' faces.
你不能挂着
你在我身上的脆弱
顾客的脸。
Well, they don't
seem to mind.
嗯，他们不
似乎介意。
Oh, I have disgusting
clientele
哦，我有恶心
顾客群
who spend their
money freely.
谁花他们的
钱自由。
Ha-ha, aye, aye,
Captain.
哈哈，是啊是啊，
队长。
Because I'd hate for
a certain living arrangement
因为我讨厌
一定的生活安排
meaning yours, to interfere
with said money spending.
意思是你的，干涉
用所说的钱花。
What the barnacles?
什么是藤壶？
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
Why's your bed in me office?
为什么你的床在我办公室？
It was getting kind of
crowded in the kitchen...
它变得有点
厨房里挤满了人……
So I moved in here.
所以我搬到了这里。
You can't stay
in here.
你不能留下来
在这里。
These are me private
quarters, boy.
这些是我私人的
宿舍，男孩。
The only place I can escape
for solitude during the day.
我唯一可以逃离的地方
为了白天的孤独。
But I'll only be
here at night.
但我只会
晚上在这里。
Please, Mr. Krabs?
请问，蟹老板？
I won't get in your
way, please.
我不会进入你的
拜托。
Oh, OK.
哦，好吧。
But I'll have to raise
your rent.
但我必须提高
你的租金。
Oh, thank you, Mr.-
哦，谢谢你，先生-
My parents.
我的父母。
Your parents?
你的父母？
Mom, Dad, come on in.
爸爸妈妈，快进来吧。
And this is the guest room.
这是客房。
Mom, Dad, Mr. Krabs.
妈妈，爸爸，蟹老板。
Oh, hello.
哦，你好。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Well, I'll let you
two get settled.
好吧，我让你
两个安顿下来。
Is this your snail?
这是你的蜗牛吗？
Bad boy, no.
坏孩子，不。
Put that thing
on a leash.
把那个东西
拴在皮带上。
Squidward.
章鱼哥。
Who put these fancy smelling
soaps in the restroom?
谁放了这些奇特的气味
洗手间里有肥皂吗？
The same person who
knitted these napkin holders
同一个人
编织这些餐巾架
and embroidered the menus.
并绣上菜单。
Arg.
精氨酸。
That boy's takin' the manliness
out of me restaurant.
那个男孩很有男子气概
走出我的餐厅。
What? Oh, he didn't.
什么？哦，他没有。
Floral print curtains
in me office?
花卉印花窗帘
在我办公室吗？
That's it, that's
the last straw.
就是这样，就是这样
最后一根稻草。
I'm not putting up
with this any longer.
我不放
不再这样了。
Oh, I... I'm sorry.
哦，我……对不起。
I didn't know...
我不知道...
What's going on
in here?
发生了什么事
在这里？
What the?
什么？
Thanks, SpongeBob.
谢谢，海绵宝宝。
If I could reach,
I'd do it myself.
如果我能到达的话
我会自己做。
Me customers.
我的顾客。
Gone, gone.
走了，走了。
All they wanted
was to give me...
他们想要的一切
是为了给我...
their money.
他们的钱。
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
Pack your bags, boy,
your movin' out.
收拾好你的行囊，孩子，
你要搬出去了。
What the?
什么？
SpongeBob, what are
you doing here?
海绵宝宝，什么是
你在这里做什么？
Oh, Mr. Krabs
kicked me out
哦，蟹老板
把我踢出去了
so now we're neighbors again.
所以现在我们又成为邻居了。
Hey, my drums.
嘿，我的鼓。
No...!
不...！
Squidward!
章鱼哥！
Narrator: It is a cold
and windy day.
旁白：感冒了
和刮风的日子。
Bikini bottom is covered
in goose bumps.
比基尼底部被遮盖
浑身起鸡皮疙瘩。
Oh, it's freezing in here.
哦，这里很冷。
Not if you get
up and exercise.
不是如果你得到
起来锻炼。
Hup-two, hup-two.
哈普二，哈普二。
Yes, sir, my buns
are nice and toasty.
是的，先生，我的面包
很好吃。
I'm so glad
I don't eat here.
我很高兴
我不在这里吃饭。
Brr...!
呜……！
How cold does Krabs keep
this place, anyway?
螃蟹的保冷温度是多少
无论如何，这个地方？
62 degrees?
62度？
Oh, that cheapskate.
哦，那个小气鬼。
I'm going to set it
to a toasty 63.
我去设置一下
到烤面包63。
Huh?
啊？
Who... touched...
谁……触动了……
me thermostat?
我恒温器？
Oh, thanks a...
哦，谢谢一个...
You're welcome,
Squidward.
不客气，
章鱼哥。
Mr. Squidward, you're
always goin' on
章鱼哥先生，你是
总是在继续
about your book club.
关于你的读书俱乐部。
Read this.
读一下这个。
Squidward: "Do not touch
thermostat ever."
章鱼哥：“别碰
恒温器曾经。”
Heat costs money!
取暖要花钱啊！
There's two ways to get
on me bad side, boys.
有两种方法可以获得
对我来说是不好的一面，孩子们。
I don't like kids
playing in me yard.
我不喜欢孩子
在我的院子里玩。
And nobody but me touches
me thermostat.
除了我之外没有人碰触
我恒温器。
That's totally
selfish.
这完全是
自私。
Yeah, your yard
is really fun.
是的，你的院子
真的很有趣。
There are kids playing
on it right now.
有孩子在玩耍
现在就在上面。
What?
什么？
Mr. Krabs: Hey, you kids
get off of my lawn.
蟹老板：嘿，你们这些孩子
从我的草坪上滚出去。
Male voice: That's right,
run, Krabs
男声：没错，
跑吧，蟹蟹
for I have found your
Achilles heel.
因为我已经找到了你的
阿喀琉斯之踵。
I'll freeze you out of business
我会让你失业
and I'll do it with your
precious thermostat.
我会用你的
珍贵的恒温器。
What the... Oh, no!
这什么……哦，不！
Code red!
红色代码！
Abandon ship, abandon ship!
弃船弃船！
Plankton  :
No matter.
浮游生物：
没关系。
In four to six hours
四到六个小时内
I will have my revenge.
我会报仇的。
I'm gonna go recover
from hypothermia.
我要去康复
来自体温过低。
Hippo-what-ia?
河马-什么-ia？
What does that mean?
这意味着什么？
It means he's
a big fat crybaby.
这意味着他是
一个大胖爱哭鬼。
Locked in again.
又被锁了。
That Krusty old barnacle might
keep me from his secret formula
那个 Krusty 老藤壶可能
让我远离他的秘密配方
but I'd like to see him
serve a Krabby Patty
但我想见他
供应蟹肉饼
when I'm done with this place.
当我完成这个地方的时候。
Into every life
走进每一个生活
a little rain must fall, Krabs.
一定要下点小雨，蟹蟹。
It's just business.
这只是生意。
Well, maybe it  is  personal.
好吧，也许这是个人的。
I'm touching your thermostat.
我正在触摸你的恒温器。
Mr. Krabs: No, no.
蟹老板：不，不。
Someone... Touching...
有人……感人……
Thermostat.
恒温器。
Oh, I meant to bring
a sweater.
哦，我本来想带
一件毛衣。
It's colder than yesterday.
比昨天冷了。
That's why
I wore mittens.
这就是为什么
我戴着手套。
Mmm, toasty.
嗯，烤面包。
Huh?
啊？
Mr. Krabs: Morning, boys.
蟹老板：早上好，孩子们。
Lock's a bit sticky
this morning.
锁有点粘
今天早上。
Is it cold in here
or is it just me?
这里冷吗
或者只是我？
Well, get to work.
好吧，开始工作吧。
What?
什么？
Aye, aye, Mr. Krabs,
whoa.
是啊，是啊，蟹老板先生，
哇哦。
Whoa!
哇！
SpongeBob: Pardon me.
海绵宝宝：请原谅我。
All right, quit
clowning around
and get to work.
好吧，退出吧
小丑表演
并开始工作。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
As soon as you turn
the heat up.
只要你一转身
热度上升。
Mr. Krabs: The temperature
stays at 62 degrees.
蟹老板：温度
保持在62度。
There's icicles hanging
from the ceiling.
上面还挂着冰柱
从天花板上。
I don't care if "Santee"
Claus and Jack Frost
我不在乎“桑蒂”是否
克劳斯和杰克·弗罗斯特
are having ice cream cones.
正在吃蛋卷冰淇淋。
Don't... touch...
别……碰……
the thermostat!
恒温器！
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
啊啊啊啊啊！
I knew you'd be too
stubborn to turn the heat up.
我就知道你也会的
固执地把暖气调高。
Let's see how long you keep
those customers
让我们看看你能坚持多久
那些顾客
when you give them
the cold shoulder.
当你给他们
冷遇。
What's taking so long?
什么事要花这么长时间？
Quit your lollygaggin'
and get a move on.
别再胡闹了
并继续前进。
Whoa...
哇...
Order up.
订购吧。
Let's get out of here.
我们离开这里吧。
Customer: Yeah, let's go.
顾客：是啊，我们走吧。
Plankton: Yes, flee
that frozen wasteland.
浮游生物：是的，逃跑
那片冰冻的荒原
Warmth and joy have
left your lives.
温暖和欢乐已经有了
离开了你们的生活。
Hey, buddy
嘿，伙计
you wanna eat
at the Chum Bucket?
你想吃吗
在密友桶里？
Plankton: Fine,
at least Krab's place
is deserted.
浮游生物：很好，
至少是蟹蟹的地方
荒无人烟。
Hey, the customers
are coming back.
嘿，顾客们
正在回来。
I don't understand.
我不明白。
What's bringing them back?
是什么让他们回来？
What the...?
什么……？
Just put those patties
back when you're done.
只要把那些肉饼放进去
完成后回来。
Can do, Mr. Krabs.
可以，蟹老板。
I'm really glad
I don't eat here.
我真的很高兴
我不在这里吃饭。
Order up.
订购吧。
Where's my food?
我的食物在哪里？
Mmm.
嗯。
I want my Krabby flabby.
我想要我的蟹蟹松软的。
Coming right up, sir.
马上就上来，先生。
Ow-ow!
噢噢！
Delicious.
可口的。
Yay!
耶！
Wow, that looks
like fun.
哇，看起来
喜欢好玩。
I'll have two Krabby
Patties, but don't cook them.
我要两只蟹蟹
馅饼，但不要煮它们。
I'll have two frozen
Krabby Patties too.
我要两个冷冻的
还有蟹黄饼。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
I want patty skates.
我想要馅饼溜冰鞋。
Customer: I need two
patties now.
顾客：我需要两个
现在是馅饼。
It's beautiful.
很美丽。
I'm selling twice
as many patties
我卖两次
尽可能多的肉饼
and I don't even
have to cook 'em.
我什至不
必须把它们煮熟。
This is the happiest
and most cost effective day
这是最幸福的
也是最具成本效益的一天
of me whole life.
我的一生。
Plankton: No!
浮游生物：不！
How is this possible?
这怎么可能？
I freeze his place solid
我冻结了他的位置
and he turns it
into an ice rink.
他转动它
进入溜冰场。
He's making more money
than ever.
他赚更多的钱
比以往任何时候。
Female voice: That's because,
unlike you
女声：那是因为，
不像你
he's a good businessman.
他是一个好商人。
Well, if it isn't the wind
beneath my wings.
好吧，如果不是风
在我的翅膀下。
I don't understand why
you don't just steal
我不明白为什么
你不只是偷
a Krabby Patty in all
that confusion.
总共有一个蟹肉饼
那种混乱。
I'll be right back.
我马上回来。
I don't know why
I encourage him.
我不知道为什么
我鼓励他。
Mr. Krabs:
This is fantastic.
蟹老板先生：
这太棒了。
The local hockey team
is payin' me
to practice here.
当地曲棍球队
正在付钱给我
在这里练习。
Coming through.
即将通过。
Hi, Patrick.
嗨，帕特里克。
: Hi, SpongeBob.
: 嗨，海绵宝宝。
Where'd the puck go?
冰球去哪儿了？
Holy shrimp.
圣虾。
Plankton.
浮游生物。
Plankton: I did it.
浮游生物：我做到了。
I've finally
got a Krabby Patty.
我终于
得到了蟹肉饼。
SpongeBob: Not quite, Plankton.
海绵宝宝：不完全是，浮游生物。
You'll have to get
past me first.
你必须得到
先从我身边经过。
There's the puck.
冰球就在那里。
That little square guy has it.
那个方方正正的小家伙就有了。
Get him.
抓住他。
Yikes!
哎呀！
Yes.
是的。
Whoa-oh-oh-oh!
哇哦哦哦！
You're mine now, Plankton.
你现在是我的了，浮游生物。
You won't get away
with this, Plankton.
你不会逃脱
有了这个，浮游生物。
Hey, SpongeBob,
long time no see.
嘿，海绵宝宝，
好久不见。
What you been up to?
你最近在忙什么？
How was your weekend?
你周末过得怎么样？
Oh, my weekend
was fabulous.
哦，我的周末
太棒了。
Thank you for asking.
谢谢你的询问。
Patrick and I went
jellyfishing but I lost my net.
帕特里克和我去了
捕水母，但我丢了网。
Ha, so I tried to borrow one
from Squidward but he didn't
have one
哈，所以我想借一个
来自章鱼哥但他没有
有一个
and then when he yelled at me,
he swallowed a bug.
然后当他对我大喊大叫时
他吞下了一只虫子。
Swallowed a bug.
吞下了一只虫子。
Fascinating.
迷人。
Well, gotta go.
嗯，该走了。
Better luck next time,
SpongeBob.
下次好运，
海绵宝宝。
There's the puck, Eh,
get it.
那里有冰球，呃，
得到它。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
Whoa!
哇！
Grrr... Ah!
咕噜……啊！
Ow.
噢。
Hold it right there, mister.
就在那里，先生。
Huh?
啊？
Phew! Uh.
唷！呃。
Yes, I'm gonna make it.
是的，我会成功的。
SpongeBob: Gotcha, Plankton.
海绵宝宝：明白了，浮游生物。
Plankton: On the contrary...
浮游生物：恰恰相反……
It is I who has you.
拥有你的是我。
The clamboni.
兰博尼。
Run for it!
奔跑吧！
Run you fools, run.
你们这些傻瓜，快跑，快跑。
♪ La-da, doo, da-da-dee,
la-doo ♪
♪ 拉达、杜、达达迪、
拉杜 ♪
Mmm...
嗯...
It's working.
它正在发挥作用。
I'm actually going to get
a Krabby Patty.
我实际上会得到
蟹肉饼。
Crowd: Ah, ah!
众人：啊啊啊！
Come on, get out of the way.
来吧，让开。
You're blocking the exit.
你挡住了出口。
No, no!
不，不！
Mr. Krabs: I'll take that.
蟹老板：我接受。
Brilliant idea to block
the exit with your body,
SpongeBob.
阻止的好主意
你的身体的出口，
海绵宝宝。
Um, thank you Mr. Krabs.
嗯，谢谢蟹老板。
You lose again, Plankton.
你又输了，浮游生物。
I'm not giving up yet, Krabs.
我还没有放弃，蟹蟹。
I've still got my secret weapon.
我仍然有我的秘密武器。
The thermostat!
恒温器！
Thermostat?
恒温器？
That's right, Krabs.
没错，蟹蟹。
It was I who froze
the Krusty Krab.
是我被冻住了
蟹堡王。
You see?
你看？
You gone too far
this time, Plankton.
你走得太远了
这次是浮游生物。
You can pummel me employees...
你可以殴打我的员工...
try to destroy me restaurant...
试图毁掉我的餐厅...
but nobody messes
with me thermostat.
但没人乱搞
和我一起恒温器。
Grrr...
咕噜……
See, Krabs
瞧，蟹蟹
you can't defeat me.
你无法打败我。
Whoo!
呼！
Whoa!
哇！
Here's your Krabby Patty
and lemonade, Mr. Krabs.
这是你的蟹肉饼
还有柠檬水，蟹老板。
Thank you, lad.
谢谢你，小伙子。
Well, well, if it
isn't Plankton.
好吧好吧，如果是的话
不是浮游生物。
You know I should thank you.
你知道我应该感谢你。
What with the ice rink
溜冰场有什么用
and now the swimming pool
gimmick
现在是游泳池
噱头
I'm making more money
than I ever did with the old
Krusty Krab.
我赚更多的钱
比我对旧的做过的
蟹堡王。
Hey, you got any more
good ideas?
嘿嘿，你还有吗
好主意？